(Sheldon:)I must say, Leonard...
(Sheldon:)...when I first heard your idea
for Giant Jenga I was skeptical.
(Leonard:)I can't blame you,
Tiny Twister was a complete bust.
Oh. But I was wrong.
(Sheldon:)The looming threat of being crushed
under a pile of lumber...
(Sheldon:)...does add a certain spice.
(Sheldon:)I've never felt so alive.
Oh, hello, Alex. Let me go get you
last night's recordings.
(Leonard:)What recordings?
(Sheldon:)Remember when you told me
I talk in my sleep?
(Sheldon:)It occurred to me that like most
things I say, it's probably pure gold.
(Sheldon:)So I started recording it all and...
(Sheldon:)...now Alex gets to comb through...
(Sheldon:)...eight hours of what I like to call
"Sheldon After Dark."
- Hey, Leonard.
- Hey.
(Leonard:)Just playing a little Giant Jenga.
(Alex:)I know, I'm the one who
had to buy him the helmet.
So do you have plans this weekend?
(Leonard:)Most of Saturday's gonna be figuring out
where to put this game when we're done.
(Leonard:)How about you?
I'm gonna go hear Kip Thorne give a
lecture about subatomic space-time.
(Leonard:)Oh, that's his take on John Wheeler's
quantum foam. That should be great.
Well, you can come with me.
(Leonard:)I'd love to, but I'm supposed to
hang out with Penny.
- Well, bring her.
- Oh, she's not really into in that kind of stuff.
(Alex:)Well, if you want to hear about the lecture,
I can tell you all about it at work...
(Alex:)...or, you know, over dinner sometime.
(Leonard (jumping and knocking over the Jenga):)What?
Giant Jenga! I win!